<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call center assistant</title>
    <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Call center assistant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/general/</guid>
      <description>What is a coronavirus? Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses which may cause illness in animals or humans. In humans, several coronaviruses are known to cause respiratory infections ranging from the common cold to more severe diseases such as Middle East Respiratory Syndrome (MERS) and Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS). The most recently discovered coronavirus causes coronavirus disease COVID-19.
What is COVID-19? COVID-19 is the infectious disease caused by the most recently discovered coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Procedure (Patient Transfer)</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/emergencyprocedurehomhos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/emergencyprocedurehomhos/</guid>
      <description>Ask patient if he would like to get transferred to RHUH or to another hospital.
If patient requests to get transferred to another hospital other than RHUH Provide the patient with the hospitals that accommodate COVID19 positive patient and inform them that they will have to coordinate with them by themselves.
Hospitals that accommodate COVID19 patients (SOON)
 If patient wants to get transferred to RHUH  patient will be put on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isolation Procedure</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/isolationprocedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/isolationprocedure/</guid>
      <description>Ask patient the following questions
  Have you recently traveled to an area with known local spread of COVID-19? (Iran, Italy, spain, USA, France, UAE, …)
  Have you come into close contact (within 1.5 meters) with someone who has a laboratory confirmed or suspected COVID-19 diagnosis within the last 14 days?
  Are you a first responder, healthcare worker, or employee or attendee of a child or adult care facility?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spread</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/spread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/spread/</guid>
      <description>How does COVID-19 spread? People can catch COVID-19 from others who have the virus.
The disease can spread from person to person through small droplets from the nose or mouth which are spread when a person with COVID-19 coughs or exhales. These droplets land on objects and surfaces around the person. Other people then catch COVID-19 by touching these objects or surfaces, then touching their eyes, nose or mouth. People can also catch COVID-19 if they breathe in droplets from a person with COVID-19 who coughs out or exhales droplets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symptoms And Test</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/symptomsntest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/symptomsntest/</guid>
      <description>What are the symptoms of COVID-19? The most common symptoms of COVID-19 are:
 Fever Fatigue/tiredness Dry cough  Some patients may have aches and pains, nasal congestion, runny nose, sore throat or diarrhea. These symptoms are usually mild and begin gradually. Some people become infected but don’t develop any symptoms and don&amp;rsquo;t feel unwell. Most people (about 80%) recover from the disease without needing special treatment. Around 1 out of every 6 people who gets COVID-19 becomes seriously ill and develops difficulty breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treatment and Vaccins</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/treatmentnvaccins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/treatmentnvaccins/</guid>
      <description>Is there a treatment for the COVID-19 disease? There is no specific treatment or vaccine for this disease. Healthcare providers are mostly using a symptomatic approach, meaning they treat the symptoms rather than target the virus, and provide supportive care (e.g. oxygen therapy, fluid management) for infected persons, which can be highly effective. In severe and critically ill patients, a number of drugs are being tried to target the virus, but the use of these need to be more carefully assessed in randomized controlled trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disinfections &amp; Hygiene</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/hygiene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/hygiene/</guid>
      <description>What concentration is needed in disinfectant products – what are the most common use trademarks?  Alcohol based sanitizers : 60% alcohol or more Bleach(Eau de Javel, Clorox): 10% bleach and 90% water Detol Pure alcohol (not recommended alone on skin) Hydrogen peroxide (eau oxygene) Check this website for more information  How do I raise my immunity? A well rounded diet, exercise, and good water intake.
Cleaning clothes management? Linens, clothing, and other items that go in the laundry of an ill person:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Tested Procedure</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/testedprocedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/testedprocedure/</guid>
      <description>Refer patient to the nearest approved institution for testing  See Institutions to get tested (soon)   Instruct the patient to wear a mask and avoid contact with any person while being transported to the institution
  Attach information about Price and time of test. (SOON)
  If it is after 7 pm, patient should get tested the next day in the nearest approved institution and isolate himself in the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precautions</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/precautions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/precautions/</guid>
      <description>Why should I Avoid touching eyes, nose and mouth? Why? Hands touch many surfaces and can pick up viruses. Once contaminated, hands can transfer the virus to your eyes, nose or mouth. From there, the virus can enter your body and can make you sick. Make sure you, and the people around you, follow good respiratory hygiene. This means covering your mouth and nose with your bent elbow or tissue when you cough or sneeze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/risk/</guid>
      <description>Are some people more at risk than others? Elderly people above 70 years of age and those with underlying health conditions (e.g. hypertension, diabetes, cardiovascular disease, chronic respiratory disease and cancer) are considered to be more at risk of developing severe symptoms. Men in these groups also appear to be at a slightly higher risk than females.
Are children also at risk of infection and what is their potential role in transmission?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hospital For Testing</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/reference/hospitalforcorona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/reference/hospitalforcorona/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phone Numbers</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/reference/phonenumbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/reference/phonenumbers/</guid>
      <description>Emergency numbers:    Service Number     Police 112   Civil Defense 125   Fire Departement 175   Red Cross-Lebanon 140   General Security 1717   Embrace (Suicide Line) 1564    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/awarness/government/</guid>
      <description>Lock down period? So far until April 12th. Will probably be renewed
What day can I circulate with my car? Monday, Wednesday, Friday for Plate odd plate numbers Tuesday, Thursday, Saturday for even plate numbers (including 0) Sunday, no circulation for all The vehicles exempt from this rationing, according to the official circular, are those of the army and security forces, medical workers and pharmacists, Civil Defense and Red Cross, diplomats, media, delivery services, and other essential transport services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>