<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call center assistant</title>
    <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Call center assistant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Procedure (Patient Transfer)</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/emergencyprocedurehomhos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/emergencyprocedurehomhos/</guid>
      <description>Ask patient if he would like to get transferred to RHUH or to another hospital.
If patient requests to get transferred to another hospital other than RHUH Provide the patient with the hospitals that accommodate COVID19 positive patient and inform them that they will have to coordinate with them by themselves.
Hospitals that accommodate COVID19 patients (SOON)
 If patient wants to get transferred to RHUH  patient will be put on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isolation Procedure</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/isolationprocedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/isolationprocedure/</guid>
      <description>Ask patient the following questions
  Have you recently traveled to an area with known local spread of COVID-19? (Iran, Italy, spain, USA, France, UAE, …)
  Have you come into close contact (within 1.5 meters) with someone who has a laboratory confirmed or suspected COVID-19 diagnosis within the last 14 days?
  Are you a first responder, healthcare worker, or employee or attendee of a child or adult care facility?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Tested Procedure</title>
      <link>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/testedprocedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rooved-io.github.io/Covid19-Page/public/typicalprocedures/testedprocedure/</guid>
      <description>Refer patient to the nearest approved institution for testing  See Institutions to get tested (soon)   Instruct the patient to wear a mask and avoid contact with any person while being transported to the institution
  Attach information about Price and time of test. (SOON)
  If it is after 7 pm, patient should get tested the next day in the nearest approved institution and isolate himself in the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>